人人影视 YYeTs.com
原创翻译 双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供学习  禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
神奇动物在哪里
翻译｜Reginamoon　x6324　莱吉　吃不胖的毓杰　　校对｜木浅薰
时间轴｜林卡　贝壳　麦克的希德　孙了个大圣　大葱　　后期｜吉吉　　总监｜somehacker
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
纽约幽灵报
盖勒特•格林德沃
黑巫师再次袭击欧洲
欧洲傲罗做好了战斗的准备
霍格沃茨魔法学校加强安保措施
黑巫师
恐怖威胁
巫师的困惑
足球是麻鸡版魁地奇吗
格林德沃袭击
可能引发与麻鸡的战争
美国持续禁止
私人饲养神奇动物
魔法界暴露危险系数
1926年升至新高
反巫师情绪上涨
皮奎里呼吁大家
保持冷静
格林德沃身在何处
格林德沃身在何处[德文报纸]
搜捕格林德沃[法文报纸]
还有人能安然度日吗
格林德沃在全球散布恐惧
杜戈尔 安分点 拜托了
Dougal... you settle down now, please.
用不了很久的
It won't be long.
下一位
Next.
- 英国人是吧  - 是的
- British, huh?  - Yes.
- 第一次来纽约吗  - 是的
- First trip to New York?  - Yes.
- 箱子里有食品吗  - 没有
- Anything edible in there?  - No.
牲畜呢
Livestock?
得拿去修修了 没有
Must get that fixed... ahh, no.
打开给我看一眼
Let me take a look.
麻瓜模式
- 欢迎来到纽约  - 谢谢
- Welcome to New York.  - Thank you.
下一位
Next!
就像是 像是一阵风
And it was like a... like a wind
或者 像个鬼魂
or like a... like a ghost...
但很黑 我看见了它的眼睛
but dark... and I saw its eyes.
闪闪发光的白眼睛
Shining white eyes...
一股有眼睛的 黑风
A dark wind... with eyes.
一大团黑色物质
Like a dark mass,
然后它朝这里俯冲下来 钻入了地下
and it dove down there, down underground.
得有人来管管这事儿
Someone ought do something about it.
这玩意无处不在 已经失控了
It's everywhere this thing. It's out of control.
- 问出什么吗  - 黑风之类的
- Get anything?  - Dark wind, blah blah.
肯定是气流 或者电流搞的鬼
It's some atmospheric hooey. Or electrical.
- 想去喝一杯吗  - 不了 我在戒酒
- Hey, you thirsty?  - Nah, I'm on the wagon.
向玛莎保证了
Promised Martha I'd lay off.
是大气现象
It's atmospheric.
这座伟大的城市闪耀着人类发明的光辉
This great city sparkles with the jewels of man's invention!
电影院 汽车
Movie theaters, automobiles,
无线电 电灯
the wireless, electric lights.
- 无不让我们眼花缭乱沉迷其中  - 抱歉
- All dazzle and bewitch us!  - So sorry.
但有光明的地方必有阴影相随 朋友
But where there is light there is shadow, friend.
有东西正在我们的城市里伺机而动
Something is stalking our city,
造成巨大的伤害
wreaking destruction
然后又消失得无影无踪
and then disappearing without a trace.
听好了 我们必须战斗 加入我们
Listen to me. We have to fight, join us,
加入第二塞勒姆 一起战斗
the Second Salemers, in our fight!
- 借过 小姐  - 听见了吗
- Excuse me, doll.  - You hear me?
- 我得去银行  - 我们必须携手奋战
- Just trying to get to the bank.  - We have to fight together...
- 借过 我只是  - 看着点路
- Excuse me, trying...  - Watch it!
抱歉 是我的箱子
So sorry, my case.
没事
No harm done.
- 借过  - 这位朋友
- Excuse me!  - You, friend!
是什么驱使你来参加我们今天的集会
What drew you to our meeting today?
我只是路过
Oh... I was just passing.
你是一个找寻者[找球手]吗
Are you a seeker?
找寻真理之人
A seeker after truth?
其实我更像追寻者[追球手]
I'm more of a chaser, really.
听我一言 留心我的警告
Hear my words and heed my warning.
敢笑就笑吧
And laugh if you dare.
巫师就在我们之中
Witches live among us!
为了孩子
We have to fight together
为了明天 我们必须并肩作战
for the sake of our children, for the sake of tomorrow!
你对此有什么看法 朋友
What do you say to that, friend?
失陪
Excuse me.
需要帮忙吗 先生
Can I help you, sir?
没有 我只是 在这儿等会儿
No, I was just... just... waiting.
你好
Hi.
你是来办什么事的
What brings you here?
和你一样
Same as you...
- 你也是来贷款开面包店的吗  - 是的
- You're here to get a loan to open up a bakery?  - Yes.
真是好巧啊
What are the odds of that?
- 那就让我们用实力说话吧  - 失陪
- Well, may the best man win, I guess.  - Excuse me.
先生 先生
Hey, mister... Hey, mister!
伙计
Hey, fella!
科瓦斯基先生 宾利先生现在可以见您了
Mr. Kowalski, Mr. Bingley will see you now.
好吧
Okay...
好的
Okay.
你目前在一个罐头厂工作是吗
You are currently working in a canning factory?
这是我能找到的最好的工作了
That's the best I can do...
我二十四年才回来的
I only got back in 24'.
- 从哪回来  - 欧洲 先生
- Got back?  - From Europe, sir.
是的 我在同盟国远征军服役过
Yeah... I was part of the Expeditionary Forces there.
- 好的  - 科瓦斯基先生
- All right.  - Mr. Kowalski.
你一定得尝尝甜圈饼
You gotta try the paczki. Okay?
用得是我奶奶的食谱
It's my grandmother's recipe,
橙子味 真是
the orange zest... just...
科瓦斯基先生
Mr. Kowalski,
你能把什么东西抵押给银行
what do you propose to offer the bank as collateral?
- 抵押  - 抵押
- Collateral?  - Collateral.
如今的机器
There are machines now
一小时能生产上百个甜甜圈
that can produce hundreds of doughnuts an hour...
我知道 我知道
I know, I know,
但它们绝对比不上我做的
but they're nothing like what I can do.
银行必须保障利益 科瓦斯基先生
The bank must be protected, Mr. Kowalski.
日安
Good day to you.
那位英国先生
Hey, Mr. English guy!
我觉得你的蛋要孵出来了
I think your egg is hatching.
什么 刚刚发生了什么
What? What just happened?
但是
But...
抱歉
Excuse me...
我刚刚 在那里
I was... over there.
我刚刚 是在那里吗
I was... over there?
- 进来吧你  - 你好
- In you hop...  - Hello?
不行 大家都安分点 待着
No. Everyone settle down. Stay.
杜戈尔 别逼我进去
Dougal, don't make me come in there.
别逼我下去
Don't make me come down there.
绝对不行 阿霍拉洞开
Absolutely not! Alohomora!
贷款不行你就打算偷了是吧
Oh, so you're gonna steal the money, huh?
统统石化
Petrificus Totalus!
宾利先生
Mr. Bingley!
科瓦斯基
Kowalski!
你不是吧
Really?
不 别这样 瞧
No... Don't do that. Look.
不 不不不 别开枪 别开枪
Oh no... No, no, no. Don't shoot. Don't shoot!
怎么
What?
最后警告你一次 你这个小贼
For the last time, you pilfering pest...
不许碰那些不属于你的东西
paws off what doesn't belong to you.
我对这一切深表歉意
I'm awfully sorry about all that.
那到底是什么玩意
What the hell was that?
与你无关
Nothing that need concern you.
不幸的是 你看到得太多了
Now unfortunately you have seen far too much,
所以如果你不介意
so if you wouldn't mind...
请在那站好
if you just stand there,
- 一下子就好  - 好的 没问题
- this will be over in a jiffy.  - Sure, yeah.
抱歉
Sorry...
糟糕
Bugger.
- 你是谁  - 什么
- Who are you?  - I'm sorry?
你是谁
Who are you?
纽特·斯卡曼德 你是哪位
Newt Scamander. And you are?
你箱子里的是什么
What's that thing in your case?
是我的嗅嗅
That's my Niffler.
你这里有
You've got something on your...
[迪利维兰斯·戴恩曾在塞勒姆时期被指控会巫术]
看在迪利维兰斯·戴恩的份上
Why in the name of Deliverance Dane
你为什么放跑那玩意儿
did you let that thing loose?
我不是故意的 是他屡教不改
I didn't mean to, he's incorrigible,
你瞧 一看见闪闪发光的东西
you see, anything shiny,
- 他就扑上去了  - 你不是故意的
- he's all over the place.  - You didn't mean to?
不是
No.
你就找不到更糟糕的时机放跑那玩意儿吗
You could not have chosen a worse time to let that creature loose!
如今的时局非常严峻
We're in the middle of a situation here!
我得把你带回去
I'm taking you in.
你要把我带去哪里
You're taking me where?
美国魔法国会
Magical Congress of the United States of America.
你在美国魔法国会工作吗
So, you work for MACUSA?
什么职位 调查员之类的吗
What are you, some kind of investigator?
拜托你告诉我你处理好了那个麻鸡
Can you please tell me you took care of the No-Maj?
处理什么
The what?
麻鸡 没有魔法的人 非巫师
The No-Maj! No-magic... the non-wizard!
抱歉 我们叫他们麻瓜
Oh, sorry, we call them Muggles.
你清除他的记忆了吧
You wiped his memory, right?
拎箱子的那个麻鸡
The No-Maj with the case?
这违反了3A条例 斯卡曼德先生
That's a Section 3A, Mr. Scamander.
我得带你回部里
I'm taking you in.
来吧
Come on.
抱歉 但说真的我还有事要做呢
Er... sorry, but I do have things to do, actually.
你得另找时间了
Well, you'll have to rearrange them!
说起来你为什么来纽约
What are you doing in New York anyway?
我是来买生日礼物的
I came to buy a birthday present.
不能在伦敦买吗
Couldn't you have done that in London?
买不到 世上只此一人养阿帕鲁萨蒲绒绒
No, there's only one breeder of Appaloosa Puffskeins in the world
而他住在纽约 所以伦敦真买不到
and he lives in New York, so no.
抓了个违反3A条例的
I got a Section 3A.
顺便告诉你 纽约不允许养神奇动物
By the way, we don't allow the breeding of magical creatures in New York.
一年前我们就让那家伙关门大吉了
We closed that guy down a year ago.
严峻未知状况
你好呀 戈德斯坦恩
Hey, Goldstein.
你好 雷德
Hey, Red.
- 重案调查司  - 你不是
- Major Investigation Department.  - I thought you was...
重案调查司 抓了个违反3A条例的
Major Investigation Department! I got a Section 3A!
魔法造成的骚动
可能导致魔法世界暴露
国际巫师联合会
The International Confederation
威胁说要派个审查团过来
is threatening to send a delegation.
他们认为此事与格林德沃在欧洲发动的袭击有关
They think this is related to Grindelwald's attacks in Europe.
我就在现场 原因是神奇动物
I was there. This is a beast.
没有人类有这么强的力量 会长女士
No human could do what this thing is capable of, Madam President.
无论这是什么 有一点毋庸置疑
Whatever it is, one thing's clear,
我们必须阻止它
it must be stopped.
它把麻鸡们吓坏了
It's terrorizing No-Majs
而麻鸡们感到恐惧 他们会发动攻击
and when No-Majs are afraid, they attack.
这可能会导致暴露 甚至是战争
This could mean exposure. It could mean war.
我已经说得很清楚了 戈德斯坦恩小姐
I made your position here quite clear, Miss Goldstein.
是的 会长女士 但我
Yes, Madam President, but I...
你不再是傲罗了
You are no longer an Auror.
- 的确 会长女士 但  - 戈德斯坦恩
- No, Madam President, but...  - Goldstein.
出了个小事故
There's been a minor incident...
这间办公室里的人正在操心一个大事故
Well, this office is currently concerned with very major incidents.
- 出去  - 遵命 夫人
- Get out.  - Yes, ma'am.
[魔杖许可办公室]
你办魔杖许可证了吗
So, you got your wand permit?
来纽约的外国人都得办
All foreigners have to have them in New York.
几周前我邮件申请了
I made a postal application weeks ago.
斯卡曼德 刚刚从赤道几内亚过来的
Scamander... And you were just in Equatorial Guinea?
刚刚完成了一年的实地考察
I've just completed a year in the field.
我正在写一本关于神奇动物的书
I'm writing a book about magical creatures.
是关于如何灭绝它们的指南吗
Like... an extermination guide?
不是 是一本帮助大家理解
No. A guide to help people understand
我们为什么要保护这些动物
why we should be protecting these creatures
而不是杀了它们的指南
instead of killing them.
戈德斯坦恩 她人呢
Goldstein! Where is she?
去哪里的 戈德斯坦恩
Where is she? Goldstein!
戈德斯坦恩
Goldstein!
你刚刚又去插手调查队的事了吗
Did you just butt in on the Investigative Team again?
- 你去哪了  - 什么
- Where've you been?  - What?
- 她是在哪里遇见你的  - 我
- Where'd she pick you up?  - Me?
你又去跟踪第二塞勒姆了吗
Have you been tracking them Second Salemers again?
当然没有 长官
Of course not, sir.
下午好 格雷夫斯先生 长官
Afternoon, Mr. Graves, sir!
下午好 阿伯内西
Afternoon, Abernathy.
格雷夫斯先生 长官 这是斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Graves, sir, this is Mr. Scamander.
他箱子里有个疯狂的动物
He has a crazy creature in that case
跑掉了 在银行引起了骚乱 长官
and it got out and caused mayhem in a bank, sir.
我们来看看那个小家伙吧
Let's see the little guy.
但是 长官…
But, sir...
蒂娜…
Tina...
对不起 奶奶
I'm sorry, Grandma.
我妈妈 你妈妈 去抓巫师啦
My momma, your momma, gonna catch a witch.
我妈妈 你妈妈 骑着扫帚飞
My momma, your momma, flying on a switch.
[女巫就在我们之中 加入新塞勒姆军团]
我妈妈 你妈妈 骑着扫帚飞
My momma, your momma, flying on a switch.
[女巫就在我们之中 加入新塞勒姆军团]
我妈妈 你妈妈 女巫不哭呀
My momma, your momma, witches never cry.
[女巫就在我们之中 加入新塞勒姆军团]
我妈妈 你妈妈 女巫死光啦
My momma, your momma, witches gonna die!
一号女巫 河水淹死她
Witch number one, drown in a river!
二号女巫 绳子吊死她
Witch number two, gotta noose to give her!
三号女巫 大火烧死她
Witch number three, gonna watch her burn.
四号女巫 鞭子抽死她
Witch number four, flogging take a turn.
先去拿传单 才能领食物 孩子们
Collect your leaflets before you get food, children.
那是个巫师标记吗 夫人
Is it a witch's mark, ma'am?
不是 他很好
No. He's okay.
我简直不敢相信你没给他施一忘皆空
I can't believe you didn't obliviate that man!
假如有人问起来 我就完了
If there's an inquiry, I'm finished!
为什么是你完了 我才是那个
So why would you be finished? I'm the one that's...
我无权接近第二塞勒姆的
I'm not supposed to go near the Second Salemers!
那是什么
What was that?
蛾子 我觉得 大蛾子
Er... moth, I think. Big moth.
安静 我在录口供呢
Hey, quiet down. I'm trying to get a statement.
我告诉你这又是一起煤气爆炸事故
I'm telling you it's a gas explosion again.
在彻底安全之前
I ain't taking the kids
我是不会带孩子们上去的
back up there until it's safe.
抱歉 夫人 我们没有闻到煤气味
Sorry, ma'am. There ain't no smell of gas.
不是煤气 警官 我看见了
It wasn't gas, Officer, I seen it!
那是个超级巨大的河马 煤气
It was a... gigantic... a huge hippopotto gas.
是煤气
Gas.
我不知道
I don't know.
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander.
箱子被打开了
It was open?
只打开了一条缝
Just a smidge...
那只疯狂的嗅嗅又跑出来了吗
That crazy Niffler thing's on the loose again?
可能是吧
It might be.
那就快去找它啊
Then look for it!
看
Look!
他的脖子在流血 他受伤了
His neck's bleeding, he's hurt!
醒醒 麻鸡先生
Wake up, Mr. No-Maj.
[梅西·露易丝曾在塞勒姆时期指控她的邻居会巫术]
梅西·露易丝在上 那是什么东西
Mercy Lewis, what is that?
不必担心 这是一只莫特拉鼠
Nothing to worry about. That is a Murtlap.
你那里面还装了什么
What else have you got in there?
- 是你  - 你好啊
- You!  - Hello.
悠着点 您是
Easy, Mr...
科瓦斯基 雅各布
Kowalski... Jacob.
你不能对他施一忘皆空
You can't obliviate him!
我们需要他当证人
We need him as a witness.
抱歉 但你刚刚还因为我
I'm sorry, you've just yelled at me the length
当时没有对他施咒唠叨了我半天啊
of New York for not doing it in the first place.
他受伤了 他看上去很不好
He's hurt! He looks ill!
他会没事的
He'll be fine.
被莫特拉鼠咬了不严重的
Murtlap bites aren't serious.
我承认我还没见过这么强烈的反应
I admit that is a slightly more severe reaction than I've seen,
但假如真的很严重 他会
but if it was really serious, he'd have...
怎样
What?
首先的症状是从肛门喷出火花
Well, the first symptom would be flames out of his anus...
真是一团糟
This is balled up!
最多只会持续四十八小时
It'll last forty-eight hours at most!
- 假如你愿意我可以带着他  - 带着他
- I can keep him if you want me to.  - Oh, keep him?
我们不能带着他们
We don't keep them!
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander,
你对美国的巫师社群有任何的了解吗
do you know anything about the wizarding community in America?
我确实略有耳闻
I do know a few things, actually.
我知道你们处理巫师和非魔法人士关系的
I know you have rather backwards laws
相关法律还比较落后
about relations with non-magic people.
你们不能和他们做朋友
That you're not meant to befriend them,
不能和他们结婚
that you can't marry them,
这在我看来有些可笑
which seems mildly absurd to me.
谁会愿意和他结婚啊
Who's going to marry him?
你俩都得跟我走
You're both coming with me.
我不明白为什么我也得跟着你
I don't see why I need to come with you.
- 搭把手  - 我是在做梦吧
- Help me!  - I'm dreaming, right?
- 拜托了  - 没错 我累了
- Please.  - Yeah, I'm tired,
我就没去银行
I never went to the bank.
这只是一场噩梦 对吗
This is all just some big nightmare, right?
对我也是噩梦 科瓦斯基先生
For the both of us, Mr. Kowalski.
[神奇魔法]
这里就是新闻室了 来吧
And so this is the newsroom. Let's go.
你们好 给巴尔博恩一家让路
Hey, how are you? Make way for the Barebones!
报纸正在进行所谓的上版备印
Now, they're just putting the papers to bed, as they say.
先生 肖先生正在和参议员谈话
Mr. Shaw, sir, he's with the senator.
行了 巴克 我要见我父亲
Never mind that, Barker, I wanna see my father!
很抱歉 肖先生 但您儿子坚持要进来
I'm so sorry, Mr. Shaw, but your son insisted.
父亲 您一定不会想错过这个的
Father, you're going to want to hear this.
我找到了个大新闻
I've got something huge!
你哥哥和我正忙着呢 兰登
Your brother and I are busy here, Langdon.
在忙他竞选的事
Working on his election campaign.
我们没时间听这个
We don't have time for this.
这位是玛丽·卢·巴尔博恩
This is Mary Lou Barebone
她来自新塞勒姆慈善社
from the New Salem Preservation Society,
她给您带来了个大新闻
and she's got a big story for you!
可不是嘛
Oh, she has, has she?
全市各处都发生了奇怪的事情
There's strange things going on all over the city.
造成这一切的人 他们和你我不同
The people behind this, they are not like you and me.
这是巫术 您看不出来吗
This is witchcraft, don't you see.
- 兰登  - 她不要报酬
- Langdon.  - She doesn't want any money.
那么不是她的故事是假的
Then either her story is worthless,
就是她不要报酬的话是假的
or she's lying about the cost.
没人会给你免费的午餐 兰登
Nobody gives away anything valuable for free, Langdon.
您说的没错 肖先生
You are right, Mr. Shaw.
我们渴求远比金钱更宝贵的东西
What we desire is infinitely more valuable than money.
您的影响力
It's your influence.
上百万人订阅您发行的报纸
Millions of people read your newspapers
得有人让他们意识到面前的危机
and they need to be made aware about this danger.
地铁灾难事件 您看看照片就知道了
The crazy disturbances in the subway, just look at the pictures!
请你和你的朋友们马上离开
I'd like you and your friends to leave.
不 你怎么就不明白
No, you're missing a trick here.
- 睁眼看看这些事实  - 闹够了吗
- Just look at the evidence.  - Really.
兰登 听父亲的话 走吧
Langdon, just listen to Father and go. And...
把这些怪胎也一起带走
Take the freaks with you.
- 这是父亲的办公室 不是你的  - 好吧
- This is Father's office, not yours.  - Okay.
我实在受够了 每次我一进来
And I'm sick of this every time I walk in here...
够了 麻烦你们离开
That's it. Thank you.
希望您会改变主意 肖先生
We hope you'll reconsider, Mr. Shaw.
我们随时等候您的消息
We're not difficult to find.
您不来 我们也很感谢您今天见我们
Until then, we thank you for your time.
小子
Hey, boy.
你东西掉了
You dropped something.
拿着 怪胎 扔进垃圾桶吧
Here you go, freak.
那里才是你们该呆的地方
Why don't you put that in the trash where you all belong.
右转
Take a right here.
进屋之前我得申明
Okay, before we go in...
理论上我不能带男士回家
I'm not supposed to have men on the premises.
既然如此 科瓦斯基先生和我完全可以去别处休息
In that case, Mr. Kowalski and I can easily seek other accommodation.
不行
Oh no, you don't!
当心脚下
Watch your step.
是你吗 蒂娜
That you, Tina?
- 是 埃斯波西托太太  - 一个人吗
- Yes, Mrs. Esposito!  - Are you alone?
一如既往一个人 埃斯波西托太太
I'm always alone, Mrs. Esposito!
蒂妮 你带了男人回来
Teenie, you brought men home?
两位 这位是我妹妹
Gentlemen, this is my sister.
- 加件衣服吧 奎妮  - 当然
- You want to put something on, Queenie?  - Sure.
- 他们是谁  - 这位是斯卡曼德先生
- So, who are they?  - That's Mr. Scamander.
他犯下严重罪行
He's committed a serious
违反了《巫师保密法》
infraction of the National Statute of Secrecy.
他是个罪犯吗
He's a criminal?
这位是科瓦斯基先生 是个麻鸡
And this is Mr. Kowalski, he's a No-Maj.
麻鸡
A No-Maj?
蒂妮 你要做什么
Teen, what are you up to?
他受伤了 说来话长
He's sick, it's a long story.
斯卡曼德先生丢了东西 我要帮他找回来
Mr. Scamander has lost something, I'm going to help him find it.
你得坐下亲爱的 他一整天没吃东西了
You need to sit down, honey. Hey, he hasn't eaten all day.
真可怜 银行没批准他开点心店的贷款
That's rough, he didn't get the money he wanted for his bakery.
你会做点心呀 亲爱的
You bake, honey?
- 我可喜欢做饭了  - 你是摄神取念者
- I love to cook.  - You're a Legilimens?
对啊 但碰上你们英国人就有些麻烦
Uh-huh, yeah. But I always have trouble with your kind. Brits.
因为口音的缘故
It's the accent.
- 你会读心术  - 别担心 亲爱的
- You know how to read minds?  - Don't worry, honey.
男人们第一次见到我跟你想法都一样
Most guys think what you was thinking, first time they see me.
先给你做吃的
Now, you need food.
- 又吃热狗  - 别对我使读心术
- Hot dog... again?  - Don't read my mind!
这午餐不怎么样哦
Not a very wholesome lunch.
斯卡曼德先生
Hey, Mr. Scamander,
喜欢苹果馅饼还是薄酥卷饼
you prefer pie or strudel?
我没什么讲究
I really don't have a preference.
你喜欢薄酥卷饼对吧 亲爱的
You prefer strudel, huh, honey?
那就做卷饼
Strudel it is.
坐下吧 斯卡曼德先生
Well, sit down, Mr. Scamander.
不会毒死你的
We're not going to poison you.
你很难过
You're upset.
你母亲又打你了吗
It's your mother again.
有人说了什么 说了什么 告诉我
Somebody's said something, what did they say? Tell me.
- 你觉得我是个怪胎吗  - 不
- Do you think I'm a freak?  - No,
我认为你是一位非常特别的年轻人
I think you're a very special young man
否则我也不会请你协助我 对吗
or I wouldn't have asked you to help me, would I?
- 有消息了吗  - 我还在找
- Have you any news?  - I'm still looking.
格雷夫斯先生 如果能知道性别
Mr. Graves, if I knew whether it was a girl or boy...
我只看到那孩子有巨大的力量
My vision showed only the child's immense power.
性别未知 但肯定不过十岁
He or she is no older than ten,
和你母亲很亲近
and I saw this child in close proximity to your mother.
你母亲我看的真切
She I saw so plainly.
- 这样的人有好几百  - 还有一件事
- That could be any one of hundreds.  - There is something else.
之前没告诉你
Something I haven't told you.
我看到你与我在纽约并肩而立
I saw you beside me in New York.
只有你能获取那孩子的信任
You're the one that gains this child's trust.
你是关键 我看到了
You are the key, I saw this.
你渴望加入魔法师的世界
You want to join the wizarding world.
我也是 克雷登斯 我渴望你能加入
I want those things too, Credence. I want them for you.
找到那个孩子 找到了我们就自由了
So find the child. Find the child and we'll all be free.
我的工作没啥稀奇
The job ain't that glamorous.
整天冲泡咖啡
I mean, I spend most days making coffee,
用用读心术 蒂娜才是职业女性
unjinxing the john. Tina's the career girl.
不 我们是孤儿
Nah. We're orphans.
父母在我们小时候得龙痘过世了
Ma and Pa died of dragon pox when we were kids.
你真贴心 我们俩相依为命也很好
You're sweet. But we got each other!
你能别一直对我用读心术吗
Could you stop reading my mind for a second?
别误会 我很喜欢
Don't get me wrong, I love it.
这顿晚餐实在美味无比 我也是厨师
This meal, it's insanely good! This is what I do, I'm a cook.
但这是我今生今世吃过最美味的东西
And this is, like, the greatest meal I have ever had in my life.
你真迷人 我还是第一次认真和麻鸡聊天呢
Oh, you slay me! I ain't never really talked to a No-Maj before.
真的吗
Really?
我没有在调情
I am not flirting!
我只是提醒你 别陷太深
I'm just saying, don't go getting attached,
最终要给他施遗忘咒的
he's going to have to be obliviated!
这是规矩
It's nothing personal.
- 你还好吗 亲爱的  - 戈德斯坦恩小姐
- Hey, you okay, honey?  - Miss Goldstein,
我想科瓦斯基先生应该早点休息
I think Mr. Kowalski could do with an early night.
而且你和我明天也得早起
And besides, you and I will need to be up early tomorrow morning
去找我的嗅嗅 所以
to find my Niffler, so...
- 嗅嗅是什么  - 别问了
- What's a Niffler?  - Don't ask.
你俩就在这儿加张床睡吧
Okay, you guys can bunk in here.
不知道你们想不想喝点热乎的
I thought you might like a hot drink?
斯卡曼德先生 热可可哎
Hey, Mr. Scamander... Look, cocoa!
- 厕所在走廊尽头右拐  - 谢谢
- The toilet's down the hall to the right.  - Thanks...
非常感谢
Very much.
来啊
Come on.
真是服了
For the love of...
好像有一个 杰斯
There seems to be one, jesus
- 坐下吧  - 好主意
- Will you sit down?  - Good idea.
肯定是莫特拉鼠咬的了
That's definitely the Murtlap.
你一定是易感体质
You must be particularly susceptible.
因为你是麻瓜 我们体质有些许不同
See, you're a Muggle. So our physiologies are subtly different.
别动 这药能止汗
Stay still. Now that should stop the sweating.
这可以缓解痉挛
And one of those should sort the twitch.
拿好
Take that.
再来点
Come on...
- 你在弄什么  - 当地人管它叫蜷翼魔
- What you got there?  - This the locals call Swooping Evil?
名字挺可怕 小家伙很敏捷
Not the friendliest of names. It's quite an agile fellow.
我正在研究它 我确信它的毒液
I've been studying him. And I am pretty sure his venom
合理稀释后其实很有用
could be quite useful if properly diluted.
能消除痛苦的记忆
Just to remove bad memories, you know.
不过还是别在屋里放开它了
Probably shouldn't let him loose in here, though.
来吧
Come on.
来吧 下来吧
Come on. Down you come.
来
Come on.
[帕拉塞尔苏斯  巧克力蛙卡片上出现过的人物]
[中世纪瑞士医生  炼金术师  精通毒理学]
感谢帕拉塞尔苏斯
Oh, thank Paracelsus.
要是你也跑出去那就天下大乱了
If you'd have got out that could have been quite catastrophic.
我来美国的真正原因就是为了它
You see, he's the real reason I came to America.
我想把弗兰克带回故乡
To bring Frank home.
抱歉 别靠太近 他对陌生人有些敏感
No, sorry, stay there, he's a wee bit sensitive to strangers.
乖 乖 它被非法贩卖了
Here you are, here you are. He was trafficked, you see.
我在埃及发现的它 全身绑着锁链
I found him in Egypt, he was all chained up.
不忍心丢下它不管 我得带它回家
Couldn't leave him there, had to bring him back.
带你回归属之地 对不对 弗兰克
I'm going to put you back where you belong, aren't I, Frank?
回到亚利桑那大荒野
To the wilds of Arizona.
它们来了
Here they come.
- 谁来了  - 角驼兽
- Here who comes?  - The Graphorns.
没事 没事的
You're all right. You're all right.
你好 你们好
Hello, hello!
这是现存最后一对能哺育后代的角驼兽
So they're the last breeding pair in existence.
如果我没救回它们
If I hadn't managed to rescue them,
角驼兽恐怕就从此灭绝了
that could have been the end of Graphorns, forever.
好啦
All right.
- 你专门救治这些动物吗  - 没错
- What, you rescue these creatures?  - Yes, that's right.
救治 养育 保护它们
Rescue, nurture, and protect them,
并试着慢慢给魔法师们灌输他们的知识
and I'm gently trying to educate my fellow wizards about them.
跟我来
Come on.
泰特斯 芬 波比 马洛 汤姆
Titus? Finn? Poppy, Marlow, Tom?
他感冒了 需要温暖的身体
He had a cold. He needed some body warmth.
好了 回去吧
Right, on you hop.
他有些粘人 去吧 皮克特
See, he has some attachment issues. Now, come on, Pickett.
皮克特 他们不会欺负你的 回去吧
Pickett. No, they're not going to bully you. Now, come on.
皮克特
Pickett!
好吧 也难怪他们说我偏心了
All right. But that is exactly why they accuse me of favoritism.
杜戈尔去哪儿了
I wonder where Dougal's gone.
我来了 我来了 妈妈来了
All right, I'm coming, I'm coming, Mum's here. Mum's here.
- 让我瞧瞧  - 我见过这些小家伙
- Hello, you, let me take a look at you.  - I know these guys.
- 你的鸟蛇  - 你说我的鸟蛇
- Your Occamy.  - You mean my Occamy?
是的 你想不想
Yes, do you want to...
好啊 当然好
Yeah, sure. Okay.
- 你好  - 抱歉 不要摸
- Hey.  - No, sorry, don't pet them.
他们一出生就学会自我保护
They learn to defend themselves early.
因为蛋壳是银的 非常值钱
See, their shells are made of silver so they're incredibly valuable.
- 是吗  - 他们的巢总是惨遭猎杀洗劫
- Okay.  - Their nests tend to get ransacked by hunters.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 斯卡曼德先生  - 叫我纽特吧
- Mr. Scamander?  - Call me Newt.
纽特 我觉得我不是在做梦
Newt, I don't think I'm dreaming.
- 怎么看出来的  - 我可没这想象力
- What gave it away?  - I ain't got the brains to make this up.
不介意帮个忙吧
Actually, would you mind
把这些喂给那边的月痴兽
throwing some of those pellets in with the Mooncalves over there?
- 好的  - 就在那边
- Yeah, sure.  - Just over there...
倒霉 嗅嗅跑了 就知道 捣蛋鬼
Bugger, Niffler's gone. Of course he has, little bugger.
不会放过任何闪亮亮的东西
Any chance to get his hands on something shiny.
今天干嘛了 雅各布
What did you do today, Jacob?
我去一个皮箱里玩了
I was inside a suitcase.
你们好 小家伙们 来吧 来吧
Hey. Hello, fellas. All right, all right.
慢慢吃 慢慢吃
Take it easy, take it easy.
真可爱 给你
Cutie. There it is.
- 退后  - 老天
- Step back.  - Jeez...
- 退后  - 这是怎么回事
- Step back.  - What's the matter with this?
- 我说 退后  - 知道了
- I said step away.  - Yeah.
- 这是什么鬼东西  - 这是默默然
- What the hell is this thing?  - It's an Obscurus.
我得出发了
I need to get going,
在跑掉的受伤前得赶紧找回来
find everyone who's escaped before they get hurt.
该担心的真是他们吗
Before they could get hurt?
没错 科瓦斯基先生 他们身处异乡
Yes, Mr. Kowalski. They're currently in alien terrain,
四周围绕着成千上万
surrounded by millions
这个星球上最险恶的生物
of the most vicious creatures on the planet.
人类
Humans.
依你看来 一个中等体型
So where would you say that a medium-sized creature
喜欢开阔平原
that likes broad, open plains,
树林和水坑的生物 她会去哪儿
trees, water holes, that kind of thing, where might she go?
在纽约市吗
In New York City?
- 对  - 喜欢平原
- Yes.  - Plains?
- 中央公园  - 在哪儿
- Central Park?  - And where is that exactly?
你不知道中央公园在哪儿
Where is Central Park?
我是很乐意为你带路
Well, look, I would come and show you,
但你不觉得有点对不起两位女士吗
but don't you think it's kind of a double cross?
人家收留我们 还给我们喝热可可
The girls take us in, they make us hot cocoa.
你知道一旦你痊愈了
You do realize that when they see you've stopped sweating,
她们转眼就会对你施遗忘咒对吧
they'll obliviate you in a heartbeat.
什么是遗忘咒
What does obliviate Mean?
就像梦醒 关于魔法的记忆消失不见
It'll be like you wake up and all memory of magic is gone.
- 这一切我都会忘掉吗  - 没错
- I won't remember any of this?  - No.
好吧 我帮你
All right, yeah, okay, I'll help you.
那走吧
Come on, then.
克雷登斯 你去哪儿了
Credence, where have you been?
我在找明天集会的场地
I was looking for a place for tomorrow's meeting.
三十二街上有块地方我们可以
There's a corner on Thirty-Second Street that could...
对不起 妈妈 我没注意到这么晚了
I'm sorry, Ma. I didn't realize it was so late.
- 晚饭时我在观察你  - 然后呢
- I was watching you at dinner.  - Yeah.
你很讨人喜欢 对吧 科瓦斯基先生
People like you, don't they, Mr. Kowalski?
你肯定也很讨人喜欢
Well, I'm sure people like you too.
不 我总是讨人嫌
No, not really. I annoy people.
你为什么要做点心师呢
Why did you decide to be a baker?
因为我在罐头厂呆的快要窒息了
Well, because I'm dying in that canning factory.
那的人都是行尸走肉
Everyone there's dying.
那里能活生生把你的意志榨干
It just crushes the life outta you.
- 你喜欢罐头食品吗  - 不喜欢
- You like canned food?  - No.
我也不喜欢 所以我想做手工点心
Yeah. Me neither. That's why I want to make pastries, you know.
吃点心让人开心 这边走
It makes people happy. We're going this way.
那你拿到贷款了吗
So did you get your loan?
没 我没东西作抵押
No, I ain't got no collateral.
或许是在部队呆太久了 谁知道呢
Stayed in the army too long, apparently, I don't know.
- 你打过仗吗  - 当然打过
- You fought in the war?  - Of course I fought in the war,
人人都打过仗 你难道没有吗
everyone fought in the war. You didn't fight in the war?
我主要和龙打交道 乌克兰铁腹龙
I worked mostly with dragons, Ukrainian Ironbellies,
东线战场
Eastern Front.
玻璃破碎
Finestra.
速速飞来
Accio!
这下高兴了
All right? Happy?
找到一个 还剩俩
One down, two to go.
- 犯人朝那跑了 警官  - 举起手来
- They went that way, Officer.  - Hands up!
那是什么
What the hell is that?
狮子
Lion...
纽约比我想象中好玩多了
You know, New York is considerably more interesting than I'd expected.
戴上
Put this on.
我为什么需要戴这种东西
Why would I have to wear something like this?
因为你的脑袋
Because your skull is
在巨大冲击之下很容易开花
susceptible to breakage under immense force.
但我们还给他们做了热可可呢
But we made them cocoa.
好了
Right.
- 不如把这也穿上吧  - 好的
- Okay, if you just, pop this on.  - Okay.
这下真的没啥可担心的了
Now, there's absolutely nothing for you to worry about.
你说不用担心时
Tell me, has anyone ever
真的有人相信你过吗
believed you when you told them not to worry?
我始终认为 担心就是双重遭罪
My philosophy is that worrying means you suffer twice.
季节到了 她需要交配
She's in season. She needs to mate.
毒角兽麝香 对她最有吸引力
Erumpent musk, she is mad for it.
好姑娘
Good girl...
来吧 到箱子里去
Come on, into the case.
讨厌
Get...
糟糕
Oh, no.
修复如初
Repar...
梅林的胡子啊
Merlin's beard!
这两根一模一样
They're exactly the same.
- 一模一样  - 纽特
- Same thing.  - Newt!
别 别
No, no, no, don't!
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
干得漂亮 科瓦斯基先生
Good show, Mr. Kowalski!
叫我雅各布吧
Call me Jacob.
抓了俩 还剩一个
Two down, one to go.
你先进吧
In you hop.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
今晚的主要发言人
tonight's keynote speaker,
无需我过多介绍
needs no introduction from me.
[肖 美国的未来]
他被誉为未来的总统
He's been mentioned as a future president.
不信的话
And if you don't believe me,
看看他父亲的报纸就知道了
just read his daddy's newspapers.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
让我隆重为你们介绍纽约的参议员
I'll give you the senator for New York,
亨利·肖
Henry Shaw!
谢谢您
Thank you.
谢谢大家
Thank you!
谢谢
Thank you.
某些方面我们的确取得了不小的进步
And it's true we have made some progress,
但游手好闲是不可能有回报的
but there is no reward for idleness.
[此时为1926年 正处于美国禁酒令时期]
当那些乌烟瘴气的酒吧被取缔之后
So just as the odious saloons have been banished...
出什么事了
What's going on?
至于那些酿酒厂
So now the pool halls,
和私人作坊
and these private parlors...
那是什么
What is that?
女巫
Witches!
[严峻未知状况]
[高度紧急]
[美国魔法国会]
我们的美国同僚
Our American friends have
对有人违背了《保密法》视而不见
permitted a breach of the Statute of Secrecy,
使整个魔法世界面临暴露的威胁
that threatens to expose us all.
我不想听
I will not be lectured by the man
眼睁睁放走了盖勒特·格林德沃的人
who let Gellert Grindelwald
来教训我
slip through his fingers.
会长女士 很抱歉打扰您
Madam President, I'm so sorry to interrupt,
但这事十万火急
but this is critical.
你这样鲁莽的擅自闯入
You'd better have an excellent
最好有个合理理由 戈德斯坦恩小姐
excuse for this intrusion, Miss Goldstein.
是的 我有
Yes, I do.
女士 昨天一个带手提箱的巫师来了纽约
Madam. Yesterday a wizard entered New York with a case.
箱子里全是神奇生物
This case full of magical creatures,
很不幸的是 有一些逃脱了
and unfortunately, some have escaped.
他昨天到的吗
He arrived yesterday?
你二十四小时前就知道
You have known for twenty-four hours
一个未登记的巫师在纽约放跑了魔法生物
that an unregistered wizard set magical beasts loose in New York.
却等到有人遇害了才告诉我们吗
and you see fit to tell us only when a man has been killed?
- 谁被杀了  - 他在哪
- Who has been killed?  - Where is this man?
斯卡曼德
Scamander?
您好 部长大人
Hello, Minister.
忒修斯·斯卡曼德 那个一战英雄
Theseus Scamander? The war hero?
不 这是他弟弟
No, this is his little brother.
你来纽约干什么
And what are you doing in New York?
- 买阿帕鲁萨蒲绒绒 先生  - 我信了
- I came to buy an Appaloosa Puffskein, sir.- Right.
你来这里真正的目的是什么
What are you really doing here?
戈德斯坦恩 这又是谁
Goldstein, and who is this?
他叫雅各布·科瓦斯基 会长女士
This is Jacob Kowalski, Madam President,
他是被斯卡曼德先生的动物咬了的麻鸡
he's a No-Maj who got bitten by one of Mr. Scamander's creatures.
- 麻鸡  - 施遗忘咒了吗
- No-Maj?  - Obliviated?
抹掉他的记忆
Obliviate him!
梅林的胡子啊
Merlin's beard.
您知道您的哪只动物该为此负责吗
You know which of your creatures was responsible,
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander?
这不是动物干的
No creature did this.
别装了
Don't pretend!
你们知道那是什么 看伤痕就知道
You must know what that was, look at the marks...
这是默默然干的
That was an Obscurus.
满口胡言 斯卡曼德先生
You go too far, Mr. Scamander.
在美国绝对没有默默然
There is no Obscurial in America.
扣押他的箱子 格雷夫斯
Impound that case, Graves!
- 等等 别 还给我  - 逮捕他们
- Wait. No. Give that back.  - Arrest them!
别伤害那些动物
Don't hurt those creatures.
求您了 您不理解
Please, you don't understand,
他们都不危险的 都不危险
nothing in there is dangerous, nothing!
我们自会判断 押他们去监狱
We'll be the judges of that! Take them to the cells!
别伤害这些动物 他们都不危险的
Don't hurt those creatures, nothing in there is dangerous!
求您了 别伤害我的动物们
Please, don't hurt my creatures!
他们不危险的 求您了 不危险的
They aren't dangerous! Please, they are not dangerous!
他们不会伤害人的
They are not dangerous!
关于你的动物我很抱歉 斯卡曼德先生
I am so sorry about your creatures, Mr. Scamander.
真的
I truly am.
谁能告诉我
Can someone please tell me
这个默然者还是默默然到底是什么
what this Obscurial or Obscurus thing is? Please?
几百年都没有出现过了
There hasn't been one for centuries.
三个月前我在苏丹遇到了一个
I met one in Sudan three months ago.
虽然以前更多 但现在也还有
There used to be more of them but they still exist.
那时巫师们还未隐遁
Before wizards went underground,
我们还在被麻瓜们追杀
when we were still being hunted by Muggles,
有时为了逃脱厄运
young wizards and witches
年轻的巫师们会抑制自己的魔法力量
sometimes tried to suppress their magic to avoid persecution.
但他们并未学会驾驭和控制他们的力量
Instead of learning to harness or to control their powers,
反而衍生了所谓的默默然
they developed what was called an Obscurus.
这是种极不稳定 难以控制的黑魔法
It's an unstable, uncontrollable Dark force
会脱离宿主然后攻击他人
that busts out and attacks...
之后便消失得无影无踪
and then vanishes.
默然者活不久的 对吧
Obscurials can't survive long, can they?
没有任何案例表明
There's no documented case
默然者能活过十岁
of any Obscurial surviving past the age of ten.
我在非洲遇到的小女孩当时才…
The one I met in Africa was eight when she...
她离世时才八岁
She was eight when she died.
所以你们的意思是
What are you telling me here,
参议员肖是被一个小孩杀死的
that Senator Shaw was killed by a kid?
我妈妈 你妈妈 骑着扫帚飞
My momma, your momma, flying on a switch.
我妈妈 你妈妈 女巫不哭呀
My momma, your momma, witches never cry.
我妈妈 你妈妈 女巫死光啦
My momma, your momma, witches gonna die!
第一个女巫 河水淹死她
Witch number one, drown in a river!
第二个女巫 绳子吊死她
Witch number two, gotta noose to give her!
- 该发传单了  - 第三个女巫
- Hand out your leaflets!  - Witch number three...
你们扔掉的话我会知道的
I'll know if you dump them.
看到可疑的东西记得告诉我
Tell me if you see anything suspicious.
能认识你很高兴 雅各布
It was good to make your acquaintance,Jacob
希望你的点心屋能够顺利开张
and I hope you get your bakery.
您很有意思 斯卡曼德先生
You're an interesting man, Mr. Scamander.
格雷夫斯先生
Mr. Graves...
当年因威胁他人生命被霍格沃茨开除
You were thrown out of Hogwarts for endangering human life...
- 那是个意外  - 还是动物引起的吧
- That was an accident!  - With a beast.
然而你的一位老师强烈反对开除你
Yet one of your teachers argued strongly against your expulsion.
现在走到了这步田地
And now...
[邓布利多曾担任变形课教授]
阿不思·邓布利多为什么这么喜欢你
What makes Albus Dumbledore so fond of you?
我真的不知道
I really couldn't say.
所以在这里放出一只危险的生物
So setting a pack of dangerous creatures loose here was...
也是一场意外 是吗
Was just another accident, is that right?
我故意这么做能有什么好处
Why would I do it deliberately?
能曝光巫师世界
To expose wizardkind.
挑起魔法世界和人类世界的战争
To provoke war between the magical and non-magical worlds.
[格林德沃信徒的口号]
你的意思是以大屠杀来成全大局吗
Mass slaughter for the greater good, you mean?
是的 就这个意思
Yes. Quite.
我不是格林德沃的信徒 格雷夫斯先生
I'm not one of Grindelwald's fanatics, Mr. Graves.
关于这个你有什么话说 斯卡曼德先生
I wonder what you can tell me about this, Mr. Scamander?
这是只默默然 但不是你想的那样
It's an Obscurus. But it's not what you think so.
救那个苏丹女孩的时候
I managed to separate it from the Sudanese girl
我试着把它分离了出来
from the Sudanese girl as I tried to save her.
我只想带回家做研究
Wanted to take it home, to study it.
但离开标本泡它是无法存活的
But it cannot survive outside that,
它无法伤害任何人了 蒂娜
it could not hurt anyone, Tina!
所以离了宿主这东西就没用了
So it's useless without the host?
“没用了” “没用了”
"Useless?" "Useless?"
能致一个孩子于死地的寄生魔法力量
That is a parasitical magical force that killed a child.
你觉得它能有什么用
What on earth would you use it for?
你骗不了任何人 斯卡曼德先生
You fool nobody, Mr. Scamander.
你把默默然带到纽约来
You brought this Obscurus into the
就是希望进行大规模屠杀
city of New York in the hope of causing mass disruption,
破坏《保密法》 曝光巫师世界
breaking the Statute of Secrecy and revealing the magical world.
你知道它不能伤人的 你明明知道
You know that can't hurt anyone, you know that!
你将以背叛巫师同胞的罪名
You are therefore guilty of a treasonous betrayal
被处以死刑
of your fellow wizards and are sentenced to death.
戈德斯坦恩小姐作为煽动你的同党
Miss Goldstein, who has aided and abetted you...
不 她什么都没做
No, she's done nothing of the kind.
处以同等刑法
She receives the same sentence.
赶紧动手吧
Just do it immediately.
- 我会亲自通知皮奎里会长的  - 蒂娜
- I will inform President Picquery myself.  - Tina.
麻烦了
Please.
别这么做 贝娜黛特 求你了
Don't do this, Bernadette, please...
不会疼的
It don't hurt.
- 蒂娜  - 妈妈  - 蒂娜
- Tina...  - Momma...  - Tina...
来吧小南瓜 该睡觉啦 准备好了吗
Come on, pumpkin, time for bed. Are you ready?
看上去是不是很美好
Don't that look good?
想进去吧
You wanna get in?
- 山姆  - 奎妮
- Hey, Sam!  - Hey, Queenie.
他们叫你去楼下
They need you downstairs.
- 我来施遗忘咒  - 你无权执行
- I'll obliviate this guy.  - You ain't qualified.
山姆
Hey, Sam.
西西里知道你在和露比幽会吗
Does Cecily know you been seeing Ruby?
- 你是怎么  - 只要让我施咒
- How'd you...  - Let me obliviate this guy
我保证一个字也不会往外说
and she'll never hear about it from me.
你干什么
What are you doing?
蒂妮有麻烦了 我正在四处倾听
Teen's in trouble, I'm trying to listen...
雅各布 纽特的手提箱在哪里
Jacob, where's Newt's case?
应该是那个格雷夫斯拿走了
I think that guy Graves took it.
好吧 跟我来
Okay, come on.
你不打算抹掉我的记忆吗
What? You're not gonna obliviate me?
当然不会了 你跟我们是一伙儿的
Of course not, you're one of us now!
没事了
It's okay.
阿拉霍洞开
Alohomora.
芝麻开门
Aberto...
他应该是用更高级的咒语锁了门
He would know a fancy spell to lock his office.
好了 现在来看看你的美好回忆吧
Okay, let's get the good stuff out of you.
女巫
Witch!
- 它会吃掉我的  - 别慌
- It's just gonna eat me!  - Don't panic!
我不慌还能怎么办
What do you suggest I do instead?
跳过来
Jump.
- 疯了吗你  - 跳到它背上
- Are you crazy?  - Jump on him.
蒂娜 听我说 我会接住你的
Tina, listen to me. I'll catch you.
蒂娜
Tina!
我会接住你的
I'll catch you.
有我在 蒂娜 跳
I've got you, Tina. Go!
快走
Come on!
马上就来
Coming through!
让开
Move!
别吃他的脑子 快走吧
Leave his brains, come on!
快
Come on!
- 那是什么  - 蜷翼魔
- What is that thing?  - Swooping Evil.
我爱死它了
Well, I love it!
进去吧
Get in.
奎妮
Queenie!
你这是要去哪
Where you going?
我生病了 阿伯内西先生
I'm sick, Mr. Abernathy.
又病了啊
Again?
你手里提的是什么
Well, what've you got there?
女士用品
Ladies things.
你要看一下吗 我不介意的
You wanna take a look? I don't mind.
噢老天 不用了 我
Good gravy, no! I...
- 希望你早日康复  - 谢谢你
- You get well now!  - Thanks.
克雷登斯 你找到那个孩子了吗
Credence. Have you found the child?
我做不到
I can't.
我看看
Show me.
我的孩子 我们越早找到这个孩子
My boy, the sooner we find this child,
你便能越快地脱离痛苦
the sooner you can put that pain in the past where it belongs.
我想把这个送给你 克雷登斯
I want you to have this, Credence.
能让我放心托付它的人不多
I would trust very few with it.
很少
Very few.
可是你
But you...
你跟别人不一样
You're different.
只要找到了那个孩子
When you find the child,
碰一下这个标识我便知道 我会来找你
touch this symbol and I will know, and I will come to you.
事成之后  你将在巫师界
Do this and you will be honored among wizards.
名垂千古
Forever.
这孩子快不行了了 克雷登斯
The child is dying, Credence.
时间紧迫
Time is running out.
你祖父养鸽子啊 我祖父养猫头鹰
Your grandfather kept pigeons? Mine bred owls.
我以前很喜欢给他们喂食来着
I used to love feeding them.
格雷夫斯一直说最近的混乱是动物引起的
Graves always insisted the disturbances were caused by a beast.
我们得尽早把你的动物找回来
We need to catch all your creatures
这样他就不能拿它们当挡箭牌了
so he can't keep using them as a scapegoat.
还剩一只没找到
There's only one still missing.
杜戈尔 我的隐形兽
Dougal, my Demiguise.
你还给它起了名字
Dougal?
稍微有点棘手的是
Slight problem is that...
它是隐形的
He's invisible.
- 隐形的  - 对 大部分时间里
- Invisible?  - Yes, most of the time... He does...
- 会隐形的东西还怎么抓  - 难上加难
- How do you catch something that...?  - With immense difficulty.
- 纳尔拉克  - 你说什么
- Gnarlak!  - Excuse me?
纳尔拉克 我还是傲罗时他是我的线人
Gnarlak, he was an informant of mine when I was an Auror!
他曾暗地里进行魔法生物的买卖
He used to trade in magical creatures on the side.
他不会恰好对追踪脚印感兴趣吧
He wouldn't happen to have an interest in paw prints, would he?
一切能卖的东西他都感兴趣
He's interested in anything he can sell.
[歌曲为《Blind Pig》  歌词也为J.K.罗琳所写]
♫ 当巨龙掳走他心爱的女孩 ♫
♪ When the dragon snapped up his best girl ♪
[源自澳大利亚的魔法生物 飞行时身体会回旋]
[影片前半部分出现的萝卜形状的蓝色小虫]
♫ 比利威格虫也忘记回旋 ♫
♪ And the Billywig forgot to twirl ♪
♫ 爱人离开 留他独自寒心彻骨 ♫
♪ When his sweetheart left him cold ♪
♫ 独角兽也断了长角 ♫
♪ And the unicorn done lost his horn ♪
这酒吧要怎么点单啊
How do I get a drink in this joint?
干嘛 没见过家养小精灵吗
What? Ain't you ever seen a house-elf before?
[家养小精灵为巫师家庭中地位最卑贱的物种 因此被巫师所厌恶]
不 当然不是 我爱死家养小精灵了
No, no, of course I have. I love house-elves.
我的叔叔就是个家养小精灵
My uncle's a house-elf.
我看也是
Yeah...
[1731年起风靡美国巫师界的一种鸡尾酒 喝了会让人咯咯咯地发笑]
六小杯咯咯酒和一杯大脑冲击波 谢谢
Six shots of gigglewater and a lobe blaster, please.
所有的麻鸡都像你一样吗
Are all No-Majs like you?
不 只有我像我一样
No, I'm the only one like me.
[通缉令]
[耶利米亚·沃德沃特]
[绑架杀害麻鸡]
这里一半的人都被我抓过
I've arrested half of the people in here.
你可以说我多管闲事 但是
You can tell me to mind my own business, but...
但在死亡池里我看到了一些东西
I saw something in that death potion back there.
我看到你抱住了那个第二塞勒姆的男孩
I saw you hugging that Second Salem boy.
他叫克雷登斯
His name's Credence.
他妈妈虐待他
His mother beats him.
她鞭打她收养的所有小孩
She beats all those kids she adopted,
但似乎对他下手最重
but she seems to hit him the most.
她就是你攻击的那个麻鸡吗
And she was the No-Maj you attacked?
我就是这样失业的
That's how I lost my job.
我动手时正是她和信徒的集会
I went for her in front of a meeting of her crazy followers.
在场的人都必须被抹去记忆
They all had to be obliviated.
当时惹了很大的乱子
It was a big scandal.
他来了
It's him.
所以…
So...
你就是那个提了一箱子神奇动物的人吧
You're the guy with the case full of monsters, huh?
消息传得挺快嘛
News travels fast.
我希望您能告诉我
I was hoping you'd be able
有没有什么奇异的事发生
to tell me if there have been any sightings.
或者踪迹之类
Tracks. That sort of thing.
你的脑袋值不少钱呢 斯卡曼德先生
You've got a big price on your head, Mr. Scamander.
我为什么要帮你 不如把你交上去
Why should I help you instead of turning you in?
看来您的消息不免费啊
I take it I'll have to make it worth your while?
你就当是封口费吧
Let's consider it a cover charge.
魔法国会的悬赏可比这多多了
MACUSA's offering more than that.
望月镜
Lunascope?
我有五个
I got five.
冰冻的火灰蛇蛋
Frozen Ashwinder egg.
现在我们…
You see, now we're...
等一下
Wait a minute.
那是护… 那是护树罗锅吧
That's Bow... That's a Bowtruckle, right?
不行
No.
得了吧 它们能开锁对吧
Come on. They pick locks, am I right?
我不卖
You're not having him.
希望你能从魔法国会的
Good luck getting back alive, Mr. Scamander,
漫天抓捕中逃生 斯卡曼德先生
what with the whole of MACUSA on your back.
成交
All right.
皮克特…
Pickett...
有个隐形的家伙在第五大道搞破坏
Something invisible's been wreaking havoc around Fifth Avenue.
你们可以去梅西百货商场看看
You may wanna check out Macy's department store.
也许是你们要找的东西
Might help with what you're looking for.
杜戈尔
Dougal.
最后一件事
One last thing.
魔法国会里有位格雷夫斯先生
There's a Mr. Graves who works at MACUSA.
不知道你了不了解他的背景
I was wondering what you knew of his background.
你问题可真多
You ask a lot of questions,
斯卡曼德先生
Mr. Scamander.
好奇害死猫
That can get you killed.
魔法国会的人来了
MACUSA are coming!
你竟敢泄密
You tipped them off!
悬赏
抱歉了 纳尔拉克先生
Sorry, Mr. Gnarlak...
看到他就让我想起我的工头
Reminds me of my foreman!
你在做什么 克雷登斯
What are you doin? Credence?
你在哪找到的这个
Where'd you get this?
还给我 克雷登斯 那只是个玩具
Give it back, Credence. It's just a toy!
怎么回事
What is this?
把它给我
Take it off!
- 妈  - 我不是你妈
- Ma...  - I am not your Ma!
你妈是个邪恶的 不正常的女人
Your mother was a wicked, unnatural woman!
- 那是我的  - 莫德丝蒂
- It was mine.  - Modesty...
怎么回事
What is this?
尽管隐形兽平时性情温和
So Demiguises are fundamentally peaceful,
但被惹怒了也是会咬人的
but they can give a nasty nip if provoked.
你们俩 去那边
You two, head that way.
尽力隐藏自己的目的
And try very hard not to be predictable.
那是隐形兽吗
Was that the Demiguise?
不 但我觉得那是隐形兽来这儿的目的
No, I think it might be the reason that the Demiguise is here.
它的视线能自动分析可能性
Its sight operates on probability,
所以它能预测到很近的未来
so it can foresee the most likely immediate future.
- 那它是做什么的  - 照顾孩子
- So what's it doing?  - It's babysitting.
- 你说什么  - 这是我的错
- What did you just say?  - This is my fault.
我以为全找回来了
I thought I had them all,
可我数漏了一个
but I must have miscounted.
它是在照顾那玩意儿
It was babysitting that?
鸟蛇可以随意改变体型
Occamies are choranaptyxic.
可以变大到塞满所在的整个空间
So they grow to fill available space.
妈妈来了
Mummy's here.
我们需要只昆虫
We need an insect,
什么虫子都行 还要一个茶壶
any kind of insect and a teapot!
快找个茶壶来
Find a teapot!
抓到了 抓到了
I got it. I got it!
茶壶
Teapot!
把蟑螂放茶壶里
Roach in teapot...
随意变形
Choranaptyxic.
它们也可以缩身来适应空间
They also shrink to fit the available space.
告诉我真相
Tell me the truth.
现在逃掉的
Was that everything that
- 真的都找到了吗  - 都找到了
- came out of the case?  - That's everything.
这句是真话
And that's the truth.
- 她来了  - 回家高兴吗
- Here she comes.  - Happy to be home?
我打赌你一定累了 伙计
Bet you're exhausted, buddy.
来吧 就在这儿
Come on. There you go, that's right.
没错 我们是得谈谈
Right. I think we need to talk.
我不会让真让他带走你的 皮克特
I wouldn't have let him keep you, Pickett.
皮克 我宁愿失去手也不会抛弃你的
Pick, I would rather chop off my hand than get rid of you.
你为了付出了那么多 相信我吧
After everything you have done for me, now come on.
皮克 不是说好不生闷气的吗
Pick, we've talked about sulking before, haven't we?
皮克特
Pickett...
求你了 给我个微笑
Come on, give me a smile.
皮克特 给我
Pickett, give me a...
好吧 你平时绝对没这么小气
All right. Now, that is beneath you.
纽特
Newt.
- 她是谁  - 谁也不是
- Who is she?  - That's no one.
丽塔·莱斯特兰奇
Leta Lestrange?
我听说过他们一家
I've heard of that family.
他们不都有点…你懂的
Aren't they kinda, you know?
请别读我的心
Please don't read my mind.
对不起 我说过别读了
Sorry, I asked you not to.
我知道 抱歉
I know, I'm sorry.
我就是控制不住
I can't help it.
每当人们伤心时
People are easiest to
- 最容易被读心  - 我不伤心
- read when they're hurting.  - I'm not hurting.
总之 事情已经过去很久了
Anyway, it was a long time ago.
你们在学校的友谊真的很亲密
That was a real close friendship you had at school.
我们俩都不怎么适合学校生活
Neither of us really fitted in at school.
- 所以我俩就变成了  - 变成了挚友
- So we became quite...  - You became real close.
那么多年
For years.
她只会索取 你需要也能为你付出的人
She was a taker. You need a giver.
- 你们在聊些什么  - 没什么
- What are you two talking about?  - Nothing.
- 学校的事  - 对 学校
- School.  - School.
你们刚才说学校 这儿还有学校吗
Did you say school? Is there a school?
巫师学校 就在美国
A wizardry school here? In America?
那当然 伊法魔尼
Of course, Ilvermorny!
它可是全球最棒的魔法学校
It's only the best wizard school in the whole world!
我想你会发现 世界上
I think you'll find the best
最好的魔法学校是霍格沃茨
wizarding school in the world is Hogwarts!
废话多
Hogwash!
危险
Danger.
他能感觉到危险
He senses danger.
默然者来了
The Obscurial was here?
她去哪了
Where did she go?
救救我 救救我
Help me. Help me.
你不是说你还有个妹妹吗
Didn't you tell me you had another sister?
求你救救我
Please help me.
你妹妹在哪
Where's your other sister,
- 克雷登斯 -求你救救我
- Credence?  - Please, help me.
- 你的小妹妹 她去哪了  - 求你了
- The little one? Where did she go?  - Please...
你妹妹现在很危险
Your sister's in grave danger.
我们得找到她
We need to find her.
- 这是哪  - 妈妈在这里收养了她
- What is this place?  - Ma adopted Modesty out of here.
她家里当时有十二个人
From a family of twelve.
她很想念他的兄弟姐妹
She misses her brothers and sisters.
时常提起他们
She still talks about them.
她现在在哪
Where is she?
我不知道
I don't know.
你是个聪明人 克雷登斯
You're a Squib, Credence.
从我第一次遇见你 我就知道
I could smell it off you the minute I met you.
什么
What?
你有魔法血统 可你无法施展
You have magical ancestry, but no power.
你说过你会教我
But you said you could teach me.
这只能你自己琢磨
You're unteachable.
你母亲的死 就是对你的奖赏
Your mother's dead. That's your reward.
我受够你了
I'm done with you.
莫德丝蒂
Modesty?
Modesty.
不必害怕
There's no need to be afraid.
有我和你哥哥克雷登斯在
I'm here with your brother, Credence.
出来吧
Out you come, now.
克雷登斯 我得向你道歉
Credence, I owe you an apology.
我信任了你
I trusted you.
我以为你是我朋友 以为你不一样
I thought you were my friend. That you were different.
你能控制住它 克雷登斯
You can control it, Credence.
可是我并不想 格雷夫斯先生
But I don't think I want to, Mr. Graves.
天哪 是那个什么默然者吗
Jeez. Is that the Obscuriathing?
它比我听说过的所有默然者都强悍
That's more powerful than any Obscurial I have ever heard of.
如果我没能回来 帮我照顾好它们
If I don't come back, look after my creatures.
所有需要知道的都记录在这了
Everything that you need to know is in there.
什么
What?
他们杀不了他
They're not killing it.
纽特 你听到了 照顾好它们
Newt! You heard him, look after them!
- 亲爱的 拿好了  - 不不不
- Keep holda that, honey.  - No, no, no!
我不能带上你 让我走吧 雅各布
I can't take you. Please let go of me, Jacob!
你说过我们是一伙儿的
You're the one that said I was one of youse,
- 对吧  - 这太危险了
- right?  - It's too dangerous.
被它寄生你居然幸存到现在 克雷登斯
To survive so long, with this inside you, Credence,
这就是奇迹 你就是个奇迹
is a miracle. You are a miracle.
跟我走吧 想想我们俩联手能做多少
Come with me, think of what we could achieve together.
纽特
Newt!
是第二塞勒姆的那个男孩
It's the Second Salem boy.
他才是默然者
He's the Obscurial.
但他不是孩子了
He's not a child.
肯定是他的魔力太强大
His power must be so strong,
不知怎么幸存了下来
he's somehow managed to survive.
纽特 一定要救下他
Newt! Save him.
格雷夫斯先生
Mr. Graves.
蒂娜 你总是出现在最不该出现的地方
Tina. You're always turning up where you are least wanted.
控制住他 否则我们一旦暴露
Contain this, or we are exposed
便会爆发战争
and it will mean war.
克雷登斯
Credence!
克雷登斯 我能帮你
Credence, I can help you.
- 封锁这里  - 是 长官
- Bar the area.  - Yes, sir.
不允许任何人进来
I don't want anyone else down there!
克雷登斯
Credence...
你叫克雷登斯 对吧
It's Credence, isn't it?
我是来帮助你的 克雷登斯
I'm here to help you, Credence.
我不是来伤害你的
I'm not here to hurt you.
我见过和你一样的人
I've met someone just like you,
克雷登斯
Credence.
一个女孩
A girl.
一个被囚禁的小女孩
A young girl who'd been imprisoned,
她因为有魔法
she had been locked away
被关了起来 还受到折磨
and she'd been punished for her magic.
克雷登斯
Credence...
我能过你那儿去吗
Can I come over to you?
我能过去吗
Can I come over?
那东西杀了我儿子 我要讨个公道
That thing killed my son. I want justice!
我要揭露你的真面目以及你的所作所为
I'll expose you for who you are and what you've done.
快看 拍 拍照
Look! Take... Take photos.
克雷登斯
Credence.
克雷登斯 不要
Credence, no!
别这样做 求你了
Don't do this. Please.
接着说 蒂娜
Keep talking, Tina.
继续说话 他会听你的 他在听
Keep talking to him, he'll listen to you. He's listening.
我知道那个女人对你做了些什么
I know what that woman did to you.
我知道你备受煎熬
I know that you've suffered.
你不能再这样下去了
You need to stop this now.
我和纽特会保护你的
Newt and I will protect you.
这个男人 他在利用你
This man... He is using you.
别听她的 克雷登斯
Don't listen to her, Credence.
我是想给你自由
I want you to be free.
- 没事的  - 这就对了
- It's all right.  - That's it.
- 别 你们会吓到他的  - 放下魔杖
- Don't, you'll frighten him.  - Wands down!
敢伤他的人我要他好看 克雷登斯
Anyone harms him, they'll answer to me. Credence!
克雷登斯
Credence...
- 不  - 不
- No.  - No!
克雷登斯 你们这些傻子
Credence... You fools.
知道你们做了什么吗
Do you realize what you've done?
杀死默然者是我的命令
The Obscurial was killed on my orders,
- 格雷夫斯先生  - 是啊
- Mr. Graves.  - Yes.
这一点历史不会忘记的 会长女士
And history will surely note that, Madam President.
今晚在这里发生的事不公道
What was done here tonight was not right!
是他杀死了那个麻鸡
He was responsible for the death of a No-Maj.
他带来了暴露我们的危险
He risked the exposure of our community.
他违反了我们最神圣的法律
He has broken one of our most sacred laws.
让我们像水沟里的老鼠般躲藏的法律
A law that has us scuttling like rats in the gutter!
迫使我们压抑本性的法律
A law that demands that we conceal our true nature!
让我们活在恐惧的阴影下的法律
A law that directs those under its dominion to cower in fear
唯恐我们被发现
lest we risk discovery!
我问你 会长女士
I ask you, Madam President.
我问你们所有人
I ask all of you...
这法律保护的是谁
Who does this law protect?
我们
Us?
还是他们
Or them?
我拒绝继续遵守这项法律
I refuse to bow down any longer.
傲罗们
Aurors,
收回格雷夫斯先生的魔杖
I'd like you to relieve Mr. Graves of his wand
并把他押解回来
and escort him back to...
速速飞来
Accio.
原形显现
Revelio.
你觉得你能困住我吗
Do you think you can hold me?
我们会尽全力的
We'll do our best,
格林德沃先生
Mr. Grindelwald.
后会有期
Will we die, just a little?
我看这东西还需要某人照看
I figured somebody oughta keep an eye on this thing.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们深表歉意 斯卡曼德先生
We owe you an apology, Mr. Scamander.
但是魔法社区被曝光了
But the magical community is exposed!
我们不能抹掉整个城市的记忆
We cannot obliviate an entire city.
其实 我觉得可以
Actually, I think we can.
我还打算带你一起去亚利桑那州呢
I was intending to wait until we got to Arizona,
但现在看来
but it seems like now
你是我们唯一的希望了 弗兰克
you are our only hope, Frank.
我也会想你的
I'll miss you too.
你知道该怎么办
You know what you've got to do.
他们会忘记所有的事情
They won't remember anything.
那个毒液有很强的失忆功能
That venom has incredibly powerful obliviative properties.
我们欠你一个大人情 斯卡曼德先生
We owe you a great debt, Mr. Scamander.
现在 赶紧把你的箱子弄出纽约
Now, get that case out of New York.
遵命 会长女士
Yes, Madam President.
那个麻鸡还在这吗
Is that No-Maj still here?
一忘皆空 不能有特例
Obliviate him. There can be no exceptions.
对不起 就算只有一个人知道
I'm sorry, but even one witness.
你知道法律的
You know the law.
你们自己告别吧
I'll let you say good-bye.
这是最好的结局
This is for the best.
没错 我本来
Yeah, I was,
本来就不该在这
I was never even supposed to be here.
我本不该知道任何事情
I was never supposed to know any of this.
大家都知道纽特把我留在他身边
Everybody knows Newt only kept me around
只是因为
because...
纽特 话说你为什么把我留在身边
Newt, why did you keep me around?
因为我喜欢你
Because I like you.
你是我的朋友
Because you're my friend
我永远都不会忘记
and I'll never forget
你是如何帮助我的 雅各布
how you helped me, Jacob.
我会跟着你的
I'll come with you.
我们去别的地方 我们浪迹天涯
We'll go somewhere, we'll go anywhere.
我再也找不到像你一样的人了
See, I ain't never gonna find anyone like you.
很多人都像我一样
There's loads like me.
不 不
No. No.
只有你像你一样
There's only one like you.
我得走了
I gotta go.
- 雅各布  - 没事 没事的
- Jacob!  - It's okay. It's okay.
没事
It's okay.
就像从梦中醒来一样 对吧
It's just like waking up, right?
很抱歉 对不起
So sorry, sorry!
亲爱的科瓦斯基先生
Dear Mr. Kowalski,
您在罐头厂实在是大材小用
you are wasted in a canning factory.
请把这些鸟蛇的蛋壳
Please take these Occamy eggshells
作为点心屋的担保
as collateral for your bakery.
一位好心人
A well-wisher.
- 这几天  - 我也觉得
- It's been...  - Hasn't it?
听着 纽特 我要感谢你
Listen, Newt, I wanted to thank you.
为什么感谢我
What on earth for?
你知道的 要不是你
Well, you know, if you hadn't said
替我跟皮奎里女士说好话
all those nice things to Madam Picquery about me,
我现在也不可能重新成为傲罗
I wouldn't be back on the investigative team now.
非要被调查的话
Well, I can't think of
被任何人都不如被你调查好
anyone that I'd rather have investigating me.
- 最好还是尽量别被调查吧  - 我会的
- Try not to need investigating for a bit.  - I will.
从今以后我想过安定的生活
Quiet life for me from now on.
回去之后
Back to the Ministry.
- 我会发表我的作品  - 我很期待
- Deliver my manuscript.  - I'll look out for it.
《神奇动物在哪里》
Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them.
丽塔·莱斯特兰奇喜欢读书吗
Does Leta Lestrange like to read?
- 谁  - 你随身携带的照片里的姑娘
- Who?  - The girl whose picture you carry.
人是会变的
I don't really know
现在丽塔喜欢什么我也不知道
what Leta likes these days, because people change.
- 没错  - 我反正是变了
- Yes.  - I've changed.
我想 或许一点点吧
I think. Maybe a little.
可以的话 能允许我送你一本新书吗
I'll send you a copy of my book, if I may.
那太好了
I'd like that.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
如果是我亲自送来给你呢
How would you feel if I gave you your copy in person?
那样更好
I'd like that.
我非常期待
Very much.
你的创意来自哪里啊
Where do you get your ideas from,
- 科瓦斯基先生  - 我也不知道
- Mr. Kowalski?  - I don't know.
我也不明白 突发奇想吧
I don't know. They just come.
给 别忘了这个 好好享用吧
Here you go. Don't forget this. Enjoy.
喂 亨利 储藏室钥匙
Hey, Henry, storage, all right?
谢啦 伙计
Thanks, pal.